prfastmarketing.com 2016-11-18

# Publicity For Actor/Fimmakers | Branding | Digital Media Marketing For Twitter | Instagram/Facebook/YouTube

_This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. Please see the[Yahoo! Privacy Policy](http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/details.html) for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information._

Privacy Policy 2016

Privacy Policy We recognize that your privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use our website at www.prfastmarketing.com, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information.

We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us. PR Fast Marketing strives to maintain the highest standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all our operations. Likewise, we are dedicated to protecting our customers', consumers' and online visitors' privacy on our website.

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which PR Fast Marketing collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the www.prfastmarketing.com website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by PR Fast Marketing. Personal identification information We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, place an order, subscribe to the newsletter, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site.

Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

Non-personal identification information We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site.

Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

When ordered & Order Progress Please READ – Users are to be aware if they ordered elsewhere from other websites when an order is “In Progress” this can in-validate the order, and cause conflicting issues with our service. This however must be avoided at all times.

Web browser cookies Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

How we use collected information PR Fast Marketing may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

• To process payments We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.

• To send periodic emails We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Sharing your personal information We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

Third party websites Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, and other third parties.

We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing.

These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

REFUNDS Please allow between 2-4 business days for a refund.

Changes to this privacy policy PR Fast Marketing has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will send you an email. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect.

You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

Your acceptance of these terms By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

Contacting us If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at: PR Fast Marketing http://www.prfastmarketing.com

E-mail: prfastmarketing@yahoo.com

This document was last updated on April 24th, 2016
